in tutorial 15 I was talking about
在教程15中，我在谈论
动臂，这是一个扩展
in tutorial 15 I was talking about
moving arms and this is an extension
活武器如何使用它来创造
圆周运动，所以这是你打开
moving arms and this is an extension
living arms how you can use it to create
传播，你可以使轮子转动
我有一些很好的例子
living arms how you can use it to create
circular motions so here it is you open
在这里下来这是小红骑
布鲁斯·福斯特（Bruce Foster）的引擎盖纸工程
circular motions so here it is you open
to spread and you can make wheels turn
当您打开时，它实际上就在这片襟翼中
你看到报纸在旋转
to spread and you can make wheels turn
and there's some very nice examples I've
不必在汽车上系轮子
它可以是任何圆周运动
and there's some very nice examples I've
got down here this is Little Red Riding
然后是漂流者海盗
雷·马歇尔和我的造纸工程
got down here this is Little Red Riding
Hood paper engineering by Bruce Foster
认为这是天才的绝对作品
实际上，这是一本很漂亮的书
Hood paper engineering by Bruce Foster
it's actually in this flap as you open
您看到的价差是圆形的
基于我的机制的运动
it's actually in this flap as you open
it you see the newspaper spins around so
给你看，所以有一个例子
在这本书中，他在转转看
it you see the newspaper spins around so
it doesn't have to be wheels on the car
我打开页面时遇到了鲨鱼，他
围绕它旋转是圆周运动
it doesn't have to be wheels on the car
it can be any sort of circular motion
基于动臂，所以现在向您展示
如何使这些之一是
it can be any sort of circular motion
and then this is the Castaway pirates
例子这是基于并行
fold这是教程5，所以这里是
and then this is the Castaway pirates
paper engineering by Ray Marshall and I
带有一个小柜台的平行折叠
折叠到这里的角落
paper engineering by Ray Marshall and I
think it's an absolute work of genius
那么你有这个L形的片断，
这就是车轮卡在
think it's an absolute work of genius
actually it's beautiful book as you open
关键是一个折痕
L的手臂，以便此片可以弯曲
actually it's beautiful book as you open
the spread you see this is the circular
上下然后另一个关键
东西是轮子的中心
the spread you see this is the circular
motion based on the mechanism that I'm
就在这一点上正确，所以内在
L形的角在所有
motion based on the mechanism that I'm
about to show you so there's one example
折痕相遇，然后中心
车轮在那一点上，所以我就
about to show you so there's one example
in this book he's spinning around watch
让你一个
所以在这里我已经准备好了
in this book he's spinning around watch
the shark as I open the page and he
件，我们有另一个基础表
这是平行四边形，所以我会
the shark as I open the page and he
spins around this is circular motion
首先将平行四边形粘贴在
我们需要进行衡量，因此将
spins around this is circular motion
based on moving arms so now to show you
平行四边形的中心折痕
一块到基地的中央沟
based on moving arms so now to show you
how to make one of these this is an
标记其中一个折痕所在的位置
把整个事情都翻了，所以我已经
how to make one of these this is an
example this is based on the parallel
标志着短边，现在是长边
方面将坚持与
example this is based on the parallel
fold which is tutorial 5 and so here's
底座平整时的平行四边形
整个平行四边形是平坦的，所以我们可以
fold which is tutorial 5 and so here's
the parallel fold with a little counter
保持平坦，然后将胶水涂在
这里的其他选项卡和胶水
the parallel fold with a little counter
fold folded into the corner up here and
确保它真的正常工作我
没涂太多胶水
fold folded into the corner up here and
then you have this l-shaped piece and
这样我现在有这个
是L形的
then you have this l-shaped piece and
that's what the wheel is stuck to the
坚持那样，所以需要这个
折痕所在的虚线
that's what the wheel is stuck to the
key thing is there's a crease across one
是这样，我只需要用眼睛就可以做到
衡量它或任何顶级
key thing is there's a crease across one
arm of the L so that this piece can bend
坚持在那里有点我
看过一些书，
arm of the L so that this piece can bend
up and down and then the other crucial
由一张卡片制成
折叠并粘下来，以便胶水
up and down and then the other crucial
thing is the center of the wheel
在那儿确保内角
这个L形的块就在哪里
thing is the center of the wheel
goes right on this point so the inner
所有的血液汇合，然后您需要
得到这个圆的中心点
goes right on this point so the inner
corner of the l-shape goes where all the
就在同一点上
所以这已经开始动了，但是
corner of the l-shape goes where all the
creases meet and then the center of the
如您所见，因为它位于其中之一上
圆角件倾向于
creases meet and then the center of the
wheel goes on that point so I'll just
抬起一个角度，所以你有两个
您可以选择一个这样的选择
wheel goes on that point so I'll just
make you one
有一块粘在
后面的平行四边形
make you one
so here I've prepared the bits and
这样的圆圈在这里继续
实际上使圆圈向上
so here I've prepared the bits and
pieces we've got another base sheet
你可以做的另一种方法是一块
在它下面，所以你可以把它放在下面
pieces we've got another base sheet
here's the parallelogram piece so I'll
在这里，并保持左下方
圈下来，所以我想我会做一个
here's the parallelogram piece so I'll
start by sticking the parallelogram on
在这种情况下的那些被切掉
使其尺寸更好，然后放
start by sticking the parallelogram on
and we need to measure that so put the
胶水一点点滴下来
如果这个额外的，这将得到改善
and we need to measure that so put the
central crease of the parallelogram
一块是合适的平行四边形
向下并加入页面
central crease of the parallelogram
piece onto the central gully of the base
试图举起的轮子实际上是
举起平行四边形
piece onto the central gully of the base
mark where one of the creases lies there
在这架飞机上
并加入了仅保留的页面
mark where one of the creases lies there
is flip the whole thing over so I've
它平放，你会很好地转向
威廉，如果我在上面加上一些标记
is flip the whole thing over so I've
marked the short side and now the long
在那里，您将看到它是
实际上转过身来，当我转过身时，您会看到
marked the short side and now the long
side is going to stick to that with
它确实具有转弯运动
您可以看到，因为它没有连接到
side is going to stick to that with
parallelograms when the base is flat the
底座实际上是轮子推动它的
如果你看这件作品，这是
parallelograms when the base is flat the
whole parallelogram is flat so we can
实际上是另一个平行四边形
下来并加入页面，您
whole parallelogram is flat so we can
keep it flat and just put glue on the
看到它关闭时，它伸出来
到目前为止，我实际上无法将其修复
keep it flat and just put glue on the
other tab here and glue that down make
这样我就去拉
它的弹出窗口相当宽容
other tab here and glue that down make
sure it's actually working all right I
中等，您可以将其切碎并更改为
你走了，我有一块
sure it's actually working all right I
haven't put too much glue on or anything
它被切成合适的尺寸，所以
我可以制作一个合适的平行四边形
haven't put too much glue on or anything
like that now I've got this piece this
会落在方向盘后面
这样就可以固定它的位置
like that now I've got this piece this
is the l-shaped piece that's going to
作为平行四边形，你可以坚持
整个东西放平，然后我放
is the l-shaped piece that's going to
stick on like that so that needs this
此平行四边形选项卡上的一些胶水和
平滑其他位并将其放平
stick on like that so that needs this
the dotted line that's where the crease
如果它在车轮下面
顶住它，让我们希望它能起作用
the dotted line that's where the crease
is so I'll just do that by eye no need
是的，我们去那里了
他们说好吧，
is so I'll just do that by eye no need
to measure it or anything that top
你可以看到它可以用来制造汽车
和其他东西，但实际上更多
to measure it or anything that top
sticks on to there bit fiddly this I
有趣的东西让你知道
就像报纸转过头来
sticks on to there bit fiddly this I
have seen some books where the whole
这样的事情还有另一本书
有很好的例子
have seen some books where the whole
piece is made out of one piece of card
罗伯特·宿雾
圣诞节这是一个例子
piece is made out of one piece of card
folded over and glued down so that glues
时钟上的指针被移动
使用转盘
folded over and glued down so that glues
on there making sure the inner angle of
机制，但如果我们在这里看
有各种各样的轮子
on there making sure the inner angle of
this l-shaped piece is right on where
转向不同的方向
转动车轮相当复杂
this l-shaped piece is right on where
all the blood converge and then you need
机制的真正细节在此
较早的书可以弹出
all the blood converge and then you need
to get this central point of the circle
纸机制，实际上是
打印，但我认为有可能得到
to get this central point of the circle
right on that same point
二手版本
您
so this is already starting to move but